You're right.
We have owned more than one house.
I've talked about this with my husband.
We decided to evacuate the apartment
even if it ends up being a loss.
I see.
I told Hae Yoon not to buy the bottom drawer last time.
Since the situation is changed, I guess she has to buy it.
Don't you have an apartment in Gangnam?
An apartment in Gangnam?
Do you have an apartment in Gangnam?
We do. How did you know that?
Did you do a background check?
Background check?
I'm sorry. Of course, you didn't do such a shameless thing like that.
You sure feel comfortable with me.
You're making a gaffe.
Yeah, I think I am.
Even if you feel comfortable with me,
parents in law should keep some space between each other.
But that's fine with me.
I shouldn't have my weakness played upon her.
Mrs. Hae, it has been 15 years
since I became a single mom.
I know what the world is like.
I could tell things just by looking at you.
Okay. Let's just finish with the housing stuff.
Finish what? I didn't even start it.
I'm not going to care about what they're going to do with the house.
But you need to help them.
You have a good eye.
Hae Yoon doesn't know anything.
You must know more than I do about this
since you know what the world is like.
Please help her.
You're going to wash your hands of this now?
I can't let you do that.
If there isn't anything we can talk about, let's go.
Sure. Let's just finish this here today.
What is that look on her?
She thinks she won?
- Let's leave together.
- Sure.
There is something.
She's up to something.
I feel she did do a background check.
No. She didn't do that.
Let's believe that.
- Who's there?
- I'm here to see the house.
Did somebody put our house on sale?
I didn't hear about that.
You probably didn't hear it from Mr. Hae yet.
Isn't this a lease?
You came to the wrong place.
This is a monthly rental.
I'm sorry. It's not this one then.
It was the one in Gangbook.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
I knew it. Mrs. Hae gets rent from them every month!
She should give this to Hae Yoon.
You sure are getting old. The tube top dress looks only good on women in their 20s.
Your neckline is no longer pretty.
The collarbone should look good for this dress.
I need to lose more weight, don't I?
- Are you going to wear that?
- How much can I get discount?
- Probably 50% off.
- How much would that be?
About 30 to 40 million won.
Girl, you think I can afford this?
I just wanted you to try it on anyway.
By the way, do you get any skin care?
Do I have to?
Your brother in law is a plastic surgeon.
And you have pimples on your back.
I came in because I heard you two are here.
That's a tube top dress. But aren't you too old for that?
I just tried it on.
I heard you're having an engagement ceremony.
Speaking of that, how about you come with me on the morning of the ceremony day?
Are you telling me to be a helper now?
You can be both.
How much can you pay me? I'm expensive.
You don't have a name value.
Then hire someone that has a name value.
But you can be an exception. How much do you want? I'll pay you.
I was being sarcastic but you rode it out well.
Do I look that easy to you just because I play with you?
Excuse me?
I talk to you seriously but you take it as a joke. It makes me upset.
Do you know how much I'm letting you off the hook?
I'm not the one whom others can play around.
You're the one who treated Dong Bi badly.
She told you she won't take the pictures.
- Why are you forcing her to...
- I wanted to tell you...
that we become cousins after we both get married and I will be your elder, right?
Mr. and Mrs. Hae are very polite and well-educated.
You need to work harder to be their daughter in law.
You haven't met my mother in law, have you?
You'll get to see her at my engagement.
You shouldn't go to the other engagement when you're about to get married.
What are you talking about?
I have two sisters.
My mom didn't let them go to other engagements right before they got married.
Because it's not good for them.
Really?
I didn't know that.
Are you two trying to bully me?
No way! She's a teacher.
What she does is she yells at kids who try to bully others.
It's very hard to talk to normal people.
They have this hostility against people like me.
It's not like I wanted to be born in a rich family.
Remember that I was trying to be nice to you.
- Were we too mean to her?
- No, we weren't.
She called us normal people.
Money tells you what social class you're in.
I will be okay because I don't have to see her.
But for you, it's different.
It's all right. She's not my real elder anyway.
She can't do anything to me.
Do you think she really can't?
I don't care. Mrs. Hae is on my side.
Are you close with Jung Hoon's family?
It's your mom's side family.
His family is closer to me than my dad's side family.
Maybe you are too soft on Jung Hoon.
I met Hae Yoon at the wedding shop.
Dong Bi was there too.
The two of them insulted me. At least Hae Yoon shouldn't have done that to me.
I'll be her elder.
Do you want me to do something about that?
Warn Jung Hoon about that.
Why do I have to hear such things
like that from her because of you?
This isn't good.
We do our own thing by ourselves.
That was our negotiation.
I know I shouldn't act coaxingly
to find the freedom.
But if you don't do anything about
it, I have to do it in my way.
You will regret that later.
Hey, sis.
Today? I just got back.
I don't want to go out.
Because you don't listen to your sister,
your daughter in law is like that too.
Where are you?
I'll go.
It's okay.
I'm not in the mood for that.
Control your feeling. You're too harsh to my daughter in law that who you don't even meet.
Does she know how to be polite?
She insulted Chae Young in front of others.
Why did she do that in front of others?
She should've done it quietly or something.
Hae Yoon wouldn't do such a thing like that but I'll talk to her.
But even if she did that, Chae
Young must've started it first.
Even if she started it, tell Hae Yoon to apologize to her.
Damn it.
The accuser and the accused should get a divorce.
And I want the accused to pay for the costs.
The accused and the accuser married October 16th, 2006.
And they have a seven year old son.
For the last seven years,
the accused spent her days buying herself stuff while not taking care of her son or the house.
And the accused couldn't be independent of her mother
and so her mother kept interfering in our relationship.
Also the accused ignores her parents in law and doesn't respect them.
On holidays, she doesn't visit our parents.
Open the door. It's an emergency!
- What is it?
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- Who was that?
- It's Grandma.
My little baby.
You're adorable.
- Are you coming with us too?
- Where?
To Aunt Deul Rae's kindergarten.
- Are you going somewhere?
- Yeah.
Why did you come here anyway?
I had a meeting with someone around here.
Then my stomach got hurt on the way back.
You're so cute, Tae Hyun.
Why is your bed here?
Did you not sleep in your room?
- What's that?
- It's nothing.
How's it going with Do Hyun?
I have to go now, Mom.
I'll talk to you later.
If there's anything you're hiding now, just tell me.
- There isn't.
- You're lying.
You have many things to do now. I can do it by myself. Just leave me alone.
Is saying 'leave me alone' a trend or something?
I'd leave you guys alone, if you could
work it out by yourself. But you can't.
That's because you do it for us. Trust me this time and leave it up to me.
Fine. Do whatever you want.
Excuse me.
I never spent days just buying stuff for myself.
I didn't visit his parents because they didn't accept me as their daughter in law.
But I've done what I'm supposed to do.
Mom.
Is this what you've been up to? Suit is your last card.
- Let's go.
- I got sued.
What are you talking about?
I got a divorce suit from him.
No way. He can't do that!
He stabbed you in the back!
What have you been doing while he did that?
I sued him first. I seized his property provisionally.
- And?
- Miss. Calm down and have a seat.
Why did you get sued?
You sued him first!
What's going on?
It's nothing serious.
We can bring a counteraction.
- What does that mean?
- We're going to bring a divorce suit too.
Saying it's her fault, it's his fault.
Why didn't you do that earlier?
They acted fast. As you know, I have many clients now.
I can't just focus on this unless you pay me more.
You need to pay me more since your husband's properties are this much.
Didn't you hear from your worker here that he pocketed his cast assets?
Don't worry. This kind of case isn't the first time for me.
I'll get it back to you.
Don't just say, 'don't worry'. Tell me what you're going to do.
We'll bring a counteraction and set up the court date.
And you're going to say, 'it's not fair. it's not my fault' to the judge.
That's the process not the plan.
I will do it. Just leave it up to me. You talk too much.
It's me who knows about the law among you guys.
Just follow me!
You have a phone call to answer.
He's crazy.
Why do we have to follow him?
What he said wasn't wrong though.
He knows about the law.
- How did you find this place?
- Through the internet.
He isn't a good one.
He only cares about money.
- How much did you pay him?
- 5 million won.
How long were you going to keep it a secret? Are you an orphan? Why are you doing this alone?
Do Hyun isn't an easy man to win!
Oh my goodness. My two daughters didn't take after me!
You're just like your dad!
You're too soft!
I recorded what he said about the affair.
I was only going to scare him and let him go.
He has to go to the court.
Let me talk to you.
We're going to prepare the counteraction and send it to the court.
When the date is set, you will go there.
- Give us the money back.
- What?
You guys work so carelessly.
We can't work with you guys.
We can't refund the money. What you said is very subjective.
What a good speaker here.
If you keep working like this, we can't work with you. Give us the money back.
That's what the law says. If you want the money back, you have to sue us.
Are you going to do it?
Are you going to go with that lawyer?
Then what should I do? I paid him.
That's not important. Your kid might be taken away from you.
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
What if that really happens to me?
How can I live without Tae Hyun?
Don't worry. That's not going to happen.
I'm not going to let that happen.
It's all my fault. I shouldn't have had this marriage!
I ruined one's family. It's all my fault.
Are you done crying?
There will be more days for you to cry. Don't waste your energy yet.
We need a plan.
I guess you're okay because you can still cry.
You can't even cry if you're really in dismay.
I can't drive now. Take Tae Hyun home please.
Now that you've realized there's another life,
you don't have to rely on a man to live.
It's not as bad as you think.
But it isn't good either.
Living a life isn't good or bad.
You think I can win this?
Be positive! You think so negatively.
You're just like Sang Jin. No wonder why you guys dated.
Don't talk about him.
You're giving him a chance.
Why do you keep contacting him?
What if Jung Hoon finds out about the
relationship you and Sang Jin had?
It's okay.
When he went to the army, his friends tried to hook him up with a girl. But he said no.
He said he doesn't want to be trash.
Love isn't logical. People break
up because of unreasonable things.
If he's mad because of my past, I'm going to break up with him.
I can't live with a man like him.
Sang Jin.
Why did you come? I'm tired.
You should eat though. Let's eat.
You will study better if you get some fresh air.
Did you make jab chae?
- You're bothering me.
- I'm sorry.
Eat.
- I woke up in the morning and made all this.
- I'm eating this because of your sincerity.
Please eat.
How is it?
A little bit salty.
Here. It's some snacks and underwear.
I'm sorry for making you do all of this.
I'll pay you if I pass the bar exam.
Don't say that. I'm not doing this to get paid. I'm doing this because I love you.
- Give me your hand.
- Why?
What's that? I'm a man.
It's a lucky charm. You should
wear this when you take the exam.
- It's so embarrassing for a man to wear this.
- No, you can't take it off.
If I didn't pass the exam with this, you have to take the responsibility for me.
Okay. I will.
Now, go study.
Are you just going to leave?
I hate to leave but you can't hang out with me now.
I can have some spare time.
Let's go somewhere so only two of us can be together.
Don't call me again.
Then can I visit you or text you?
No, you can't. Just don't contact me.
Did your boyfriend tell you not to contact me?
Tell him I'm just your friend.
- I did.
- And he's still mad?
He's so sulky.
A sulky man isn't good.
I want to be sullen. That's why I'm getting married.
I need the one and only man for me.
So nobody can touch me.
That doesn't mean men can't touch you.
Our country is known as a republic of affairs.
You don't know how many people come for
a divorce suit because of an affair.
You're so judgmental.
Just because there are so many patients in a hospital,
doesn't mean the country is a republic of patients.
I love him. I don't want to do what he doesn't like.
I also had that love from you a long time ago.
But we can't boil up some ramen and love again.
Okay. I'll go away so it doesn't bother your boyfriend.
- Hope you're happy.
- You too.
Don't drink too much.
The most regretful thing I did in my life was leaving you.
You surely know women well.
What a woman wants from her ex boyfriend
is for him to regret leaving her.
Keep that feeling in your mind.
You're so mean.
So don't do that kind of sweet talking.
The man you're getting married with, I think he's great.
You've become more attractive than when I was dating you.
Don't miss him.
I want you to stop by my house. Do you have time?
The wedding gift...
It looks disgusting.
I hate getting old.
I think I should go to a mental hospital.
Why does she look so cute to me?
- Tae Hyun, let's get inside now.
- Tae Hyun!
Uncle Min Ho.
What are you doing here?
- I slept at my grandma's house yesterday.
- I see. That's why you didn't go to daycare.
Long time, no see, Deul Rae. Why did you eat my call?
How can you eat a call? You just chew them?
You use
inappropriate words in front of a kid.
Good question. If there's anything you're
curious about, you should ask people.
Eating a call doesn't really mean you're
eating it. It means ignoring the phone.
Yeah, that's what it means.
Let's go, Tae Hyun. Let's go read a book.
- Can I ride one more slide?
- Sure. Go ahead.
Aren't you going to ask me why I came here?
Why do I have to? What you say is all crap.
Why do I have to listen to that?
Why are you so stuck-up?
Your age, look, and body are below standard.
And you know I don't have feelings for you.
Who likes a 50 year old woman like you?
You think a 50 year old woman
doesn't have romance or dreams?
Kissing a person like you made me shudder.
Do you know how bad it feels to
kiss someone I don't even love?
Of course, you don't. You classify women by their age.
You don't know about sadness and suffering.
You only care about how you feel.
- Deul Rae.
- Don't ever show yourself to me.
If you do, I'm going to break your
legs so you can't ride the motorcycle.
Tae Hyun, let's go.
Be careful!
Oh my God!
Hey, you should've been more careful!
I warned you over there!
I'm sorry.
You can't even park. Why do you drive?
I know it's my fault but
part of this is your fault too.
If you came to deliver, you should've done
it fast and left. Why did you park here?
I was going to leave. And you can
just say sorry. Nothing else.
Don't talk back at me. You talk too much.
You're kind of rude to people older than you.
You're very sensitive.
It's you who did this to my motorcycle.
Oh my God. Today is not my day.
Why is this shitty thing happening to me today?
What did you say?
Shitty thing?
I'm not in a good mood either.
I'm talking about this accident. Not you! Why
are all bad things happening to me today?
The most difficult person to deal with
is the one who has an inferiority complex.
You know what? You can't buy this motorcycle even if you sell that car!
- Do you know how much this is?
- Hey, sis, what's wrong?
Sis? Then she's Do Hyun's mother in law?
Hey, I kind of hit his bike when I parked the car...
- Where did he go? He was right there.
- Why did you drive Hae Jin's car?
- He'll be done in a minute.
- Okay.
- Do Hyun is here, right?
- Wait. You can't see him now.
- Why?
- His wife is here.
- Their relationship hasn't been good recently.
- I know.
You do? I heard they're getting a divorce.
Is that true?
- They are?
- You said you knew.
Of course, I do. It's hard for him to live
with the same woman for a long time, you know?
I'm going to leave.
I hate when things are serious.
- Bye.
I got the divorce suit. You were
planning to fight with me behind.
I wanted you to be surprised.
Were you surprised?
No. That was so you.
What a liar. The reasons that are
on paper don't even make sense.
I'm going to tell people who
you really are in court.
It won't be that easy.
Let me show you this.
This shows what you bought for yourself
with my money. This will be evidence.
Only the two of us know the truth.
Others will judge our relationship by this kind of evidence.
So even if we get a divorce, I'm
not going to lose that easily.
You can give up now. Besides, I
have the best lawyer in Korea.
I didn't know you have this in the house.
The view looks so different from here.
- It's not like we live in a city, is it?
- Yeah.
This is why I like this house.
And about the house, we've decided to let
you live in the apartment right away.
We're fine.
Your father in law wants you to live in a
comfortable apartment rather than a studio.
- You have a nice father in law.
- I know.
I'm working on the list of wedding
gifts that you wrote for me.
- I heard you met Chae Young.
- Yeah.
My sister called me and she wants
you to apologize to Chae Young.
Men are blind in their own causes.
I'm on your side.
Don't apologize to her. How dare she tells
everything to my sister already?
She should've let you guys work it out.
Don't apologize to her, okay?
I'll apologize to her, Mrs. Hae.
- Did you know it was irony?
- Yeah.
I'm glad you figured it out.
You're a better person than Chae Young.
Is there any way that I can show
how good you are to my sister?
The boss is doing this kind of stuff too?
This is the most important thing.
The management.
- Give me Chae Young's number.
- Why?
Mrs. Hae told me to apologize to her.
Your mother called Mrs. Hae.
So are you really going to do it?
I don't want to do it and there isn't
anything I did wrong but I'm going to.
That's what she wants.
This is a new you.
You have changed.
Are you doing good with Chae Young?
Thanks for not asking me if I love her.
We're good.
But if I think of Dong Bi, I hate you.
A marriage isn't the final destination of love.
I can love Dong Bi more because I didn't get married with her.
What is this crap you're spewing?
Crap? Lap? Map?
It's not funny.
Be good to Jung Hoon. I saw him in the
morning and he looked so worried.
- Why?
- You two should talk.
What is it?
Why do you ask me what I'm doing?
Are you that bored? Why do you keep calling me?
Hello?
Did he hang up?
Are you crying?
Why?
There's nothing you can cry about.
You have everything.
Turn the music down. It's so loud.
Son of the richest man in Busan.
Don't call me unless it's important.
I have to make money to live since
I don't have a rich father like you.
He just hung up on me?
What a bad bastard.
There isn't a lawyer in our whole family.
Who should I ask for?
Is there anybody that might know one of them?
There is. Should I call him?
No. If Hae Yoon finds out, she's going to freak out.
But it's an emergency.
That's not important now.
- Hi, Mrs. Jung.
- Hey, how are you?
Yeah. I heard you're sick. Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm all better. I called you to ask you something.
Do you know any lawyers?
Why do you need a lawyer?
One of my friends needs a lawyer.
I thought you or your parents would know a good lawyer.
Well... I don't know any specific lawyers.
Wouldn't Do Hyun know some?
He might know some of them.
It's okay.
Thanks anyway.
Do Hyun's probably good at that
since he has done it once before.
What should I do?
I guess she doesn't know
about Jun Sang Jin.
He wasn't that big of a part
of her past.
I feel so bad. There isn't anyone that might
know some good lawyers around me.
Hae Yoon probably doesn't know anyone.
Would Dong Bi know?
- Who is he?
- Mom.
- Hi, Mrs. Hae.
- He's a lawyer.
That's it! Why haven't I thought of that?
Money isn't everything.
Why am I writing this?
I'm telling you this because I care about you.
Do you think this would be the last time you ask for money?
Damn it! I'm not going to talk to you ever again!
Why do you live like that?
It's not good for you if you
get so crazy about money.
It's not good for you if you get so crazy about money.
Life is hard and so is marriage.
I think we just have to love and
live happily but living is hard.
- I'll be here next to you.
- Hae Yoon.
What's so hard for you?
I didn't know how hard it is to take
responsibility for one person.
Have some. I bought them on the way.
It could've been so much better
if you had made all of this.
Then just think I made them all.
Okay. This is what Hae Yoon made for me!
- When are you going to be done?
- It'll take a while to write about this.
I will help you. I have to write about this toy?
Please listen to me, you stupid!
It's so cute.
Are you going to keep doing this?
Let me keep this. I'm going to bring this to our new house.
I'm going to use this when you
drink or sleep too much.
Are you thinking of doing that already?
So good to me. We don't have
time to spend together.
Yes, we do. We went to my
summer house a few days ago.
Not that kind of time.
Ok.
He's leaving.
She's a bitch.
That's what he said in the movie.
You had ambition when you dated me.
Have you changed?
Was a normal man your final destination?
What if Jung Hoon discovers the past that you and Sang Jin had.
Can you please go away?
People shouldn't meet their first love.
Who was your first love? Jun Sang Jin?
- You still remember his name?
- How can I forget?
Just forget it, otherwise you'll be
a loser like the guy in the movie.
Why is he a loser?
He left just because Suji was with her guy friend.
And he thinks that she slept with her friend.
- Did she not?
- Is that important?
He left Suji there. That's important.
It's important if Suji slept with him or not.
If he hadn't left her there, she
wouldn't have slept with her friend.
Even if she really did sleep with him,
it's not her fault because he left her there.
That's her choice to sleep with him or not.
She was drunk.
She couldn't make the right choice.
Can you forgive me if I sleep with
another woman when I get drunk?
Are you going to do that?
No. I mean I'm just trying to use your logic.
Why are you so upset about if Suji sleeps with him or not?
If I put myself in his shoes, I would do the same thing.
I can't agree with that. If it was a drama, it wouldn't be like that.
Are you okay?
You okay?
Stop!
Why are you telling me to stop?
What are you doing to a drunken woman?
She doesn't like that.
It can be a crime.
You bastard. What do you know about me and her?
She likes me so she takes
the same class that I take.
You don't know about women.
She's just playing hard to get now.
Just go. Stay out of this.
You're tall.
When a person says no, that means he or she doesn't like it.
It doesn't matter whether it's a man or a woman.
If he had done that, nothing would've happened to her.
And they would've been a couple.
That's a drama. It's not realistic.
Most men can't do anything in that situation.
This is why I don't like that kind of movie.
It's so unclear.
They should've showed if she slept with her friend or not.
It was a nice movie about a first love.
Why are you acting perverse?
Is it because it makes you think of your first love?
I know you're doing this to talk about Jun Sang Jin.
Because you're putting yourself in that loser's shoes.
I want you to be a drama guy
not a movie guy.
This is why I hate women in dramas.
It's all their fault. They make women think that all men should save women.
Doesn't a woman have hands or a brain?
When the guy told her to go away, she should've explained what had happened on that night.
She didn't say anything about that.
But after she got a divorce, then she explained things.
So you're saying that you won't
do anything when I'm in danger?
- No, I'm not.
- Then what is it?
You said you're going to figure out the
wedding gift but you haven't done anything.
Wow, you're a good speaker.
I'm working on it. Don't push me.
The wedding is soon. When are you going to do it?
You're just like that movie.
You're so vague and not useful.
I'm 007!
Hello.
Is this lawyer Jun Sang Jin?
This is.
- You know Jung Hae Yoon, right?
- Yes.
I saw you before.
I'm her mother.
Hi, Mrs. Jung.
How are you?
You didn't call me because you're getting a divorce, did you?
What's wrong? What did I do wrong?
I hate when you get mad and don't tell me the reason.
Why did you talk about Sang Jin all of a sudden?
It means you've been thinking about him.
Because you dated him and you lied about it.
You said he's nobody. We decided to be honest to each other.
You lied to me and I hate that.
Since when did you start thinking that I lied or fooled you?
Why do you ask me that?
When did you start doubting me and how long did you keep that in your mind?
- I need to know that.
- Why?
What if you tell me to go away
just like the guy in the movie?
What should I do to make you trust me 100%?
What else can I do to prove that?
It's not me who has a problem.
It's you.
What are you so scared about?
I'm not scared of anything.
Do you know what I did today?
I met Sang Jin and told him not to contact me ever.
Why did you meet him to tell him that?
You could've just ignored his phone call!
Because he would come find me if I don't do that.
I'm very scared to ask you this.
- I'm not doubting you or anything.
- What is it?
Did you sleep with him?
Do you only think about if I slept with him or not?
Isn't it more important if I loved him or not?
Did you love him?
I broke up with him because I didn't love him.
So just forget about him.
It's my turn now.
What are the worries that you talked about with Ki Joong?
- I was going to wait until you tell me.
- Then wait.
We should be honest to each other.
So all the rules that we both
have to follow only apply to me.
I'm just an avatar who should satisfy your drama fantasy.
Why are you acting perverse?
You always criticize my behavior if there's something you don't want to talk about.
Now you're telling me I'm acting perverse!
Are you not going to take me home?
You think I'd get scared if you just leave like this?
I thought we wouldn't see each other ever.
I know but I can't control my life.
I also thought we won't see each other.
Did you hear about the divorce?
- Yeah.
- What are you going to do?
- I should use that chance.
- Good.
I'll help you get in my spot.
Only if you do what I want.
What's that?
Write me a memorandum that you'd take good care of Tae Hyun.
Are you going to leave your child?
Do Hyun said he won't get a divorce unless I leave Tae Hyun with him.
If you can't raise him, give up.
I wanted to ask you this. Do you not
want to live with Do Hyun that badly?
- So much that you'd leave your kid behind?
- Why do you want to know that?
I should make a decision. I don't
want to live with a man with flaws.
There must be a reason why you don't want to live with him.
If the reason is something I haven't seen,
then I need to know.
I'm going to decide after I know that
whether I should take him or not.
Didn't you say you love him? If you do, then you shouldn't calculate your love.
Hae Jin, please don't pretend to be innocent.
If he wasn't a well known doctor, you wouldn't have married him.
All women don't get married just because they get pregnant.
Be honest with me. I think we have many things in common.
Don't we?
You're mad, aren't you?
Look at that fist.
- Are you going to hit me again?
- Can I have something to drink?
I totally forgot about that.
What do you want to drink?
- There is organic juice and soda and...
- Just water is fine.
It's not like I hate him.
He's a good man.
Then why are you leaving him?
It's him that's leaving, not me.
You know he has dated you even if he lives with me for three years.
You're the first woman he's dated for this long, amongst other women.
I think he loves you. I told him to
break up with you but he said he can't.
So I'm interfering your relationship.
Tae Hyun is important to me but not as much as my life.
I'm only 30 years old. I'm too young to live my life alone.
Though I'm older than you.
What should I write?
Write that you admit the affair with him first.
You know that anyway. I don't have to write that down.
Yeah, you're right.
You're Yuri.
What's your last name?
It's Lee.
I, Lee Yuri....
Who is it?
Here are your clothes.
Where were we?
- I, Lee Yuri...
- I wrote that.
I, Lee Yuri, will not leave Nam Tae Hyun no matter what...
No matter what?
Yeah. Let's be more specific.
Even if you're sick, have a fight with Do Hyun, go shopping with your friends,
and hang out with your friends, I'll always think of Tae Hyun and take care of him.
- Can I really follow this?
- If you can't, just give up.
My husband has more properties than you think.
He said he'd give me some if I leave Tae Hyun and get a divorce. That's why I'm doing this.
If you give up, I'll just live with him. But you're going to have to break up with him.
I signed it.
You sign it too.
Would you like to drink with me since we negotiate things nicely?
I don't hate you.
Why don't you just ask me to kiss you?
That's a good idea! Do you want to do it so I
can upload the picture of us on Facebook?
You think life is easy, don't you?
Did you sleep with him?
Do you only think about if I slept with him or not?
Isn't it more important if I love him or not?
Did you love him?
Let's meet up. I'm on my way now.
I'm hungry.
Hope you're happy.
You know I don't really mean that, right?
It's too late in the night to eat that.
I think I'm frustrated or something. The grand opening is coming soon.
- Do you want some?
- We fought again.
It'd be weird if you guys don't fight.
Maybe I should tell everything what
happened with Sang Jin to Jung Hoon.
Is this America? I've slept with five guys.
How many men did you sleep with?
If you told Jung Hoon about that, he'd be freaked out.
Yeah, I shouldn't tell him. But I
don't want to keep lying about it.
He's the one that I'm getting married to.
I want to be honest with him.
You want to tell him so you don't feel burdened.
That's so selfish of you.
There's a side effect to have an
innocent man as my husband.
Your mom called me to ask me Sang Jin's number.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Why did you tell her that?
Min Jang Do, son of the CEO of Ki San business in Busan, was found dead yesterday.
He was studying abroad in America and his death was caused by drug abuse.
The police are investigating this case now.
Mr. Min hung out with other international students there and went to a club often...
Hey.
One hundred million has been deposited into your account from Gong Ki Joong.
Make a fist.
- You will get married three times.
- Are you really sure about this?
Look. I have many lines here, right?
And I got divorced twice.
But you have more lines than mine.
I made lines by myself because I heard people with many lines get so popular.
Then why did you ask me that?
So you can know I'm popular.
I can't believe what she said.
If you have many lines here,
then you're really popular?
- I was born to be popular.
- You were born to be a bastard.
I love you, Ki Joong!
Don't thank me. I did it because you're so cute.
- Did what?
- You don't have to know.
I don't want to know if it's serious.
Let's go play.
Good idea! Let's party and get drunk tonight!
I like this guy, tonight.
So all the rules that we both have to follow only apply to me.
I'm just an avatar who should satisfy your drama fantasy.
- Girls here are hot.
- Get crazy, guys. It's on me!
Wow, they're so hot.
Hey, have I not seen you before?
I'm so excited.
- Hae Yoon
- Did you have a fight with her?
- Why aren't you answering?
- Let's just go.
You're sorry for not taking me home, aren't you?
I know you're home.
Call me.
Do you want some drinks?
- Where's Min Ho?
- He's probably having fun out there.
- Have a good night.
- You too.
I like a guy with a fat belly, short height, and little hair.
You're not saying I'm like that, right?
That is you. So what? What's so bad about that?
- Your personality is more important.
- But I'm not that bad, am I?
Yeah, you have short legs too.
A man with short legs is hot.
You know a dog with very short legs?
A dachshund!
I love that dog!
What should we do next?
There's a pair of high heels that I want so badly. Can you buy that one for me?
We need to get to know each
other before you ask me that.
The order can be changed. You buy me, I
take it, and we get to know each other.
I don't buy stuff for a woman whom I'm not close with.
You look like you will buy everything
for a woman. But you don't.
Are you just leaving me like this?
Of course, I'm leaving you. Let me
give you one advice before I do.
When a woman that's far younger than you say she likes you,
it means you have to open your wallet.
Thanks for the advice.
- What do you do for a living?
- I am a construction worker.
- I haven't seen a construction worker before.
- Me neither.
Look. I built this muscle by constructing stuff.
It's different from a muscle built by exercise.
- Do you have a six pack too?
- Want to see it?
Yeah!
- Don't.
- Why? It's fun!
You are such a shy guy!
I like shy guys.
It's good then. Let's split up.
We all know what's next.
Since we found partners, let's go.
Wait for me!
Wait!
Hey, you should wait for me.
- You're blushing.
- No, I'm not.
You're so cute and so my style.
I'm getting married soon.
What? What the heck are you saying?
Oh my God.
What's wrong?
This guy is getting married.
Did I ever ask you to marry me?
Or did I want you to tell me that you're getting married?
He's ridiculous. Shoot.
Wait!
What kind of people are they?
It's all your fault.
Don't you feel sorry for Chae Young?
We can keep it a secret. Sex, love, and
marriage are not in the same box for me.
Sure, but only for you. What are you going to
do if Chae Young sleeps with another man?
You don't know me? I'd know if she does.
The only way I can get married with you is to die.
My parents might approve our soul wedding.
You should trust me. I'm not giving anything to that man.
She's been arrogant since she was born.
So are you. You two must be perfect for each other.
You can't really say that. Didn't you hear from Hae Yoon?
Hear what?
I saw the new Hae Yoon today.
Hae Yoon and Chae Young had a fight and Chae Young told my mom about it.
And my mom kind of got mad at your mom. And your mom told Hae Yoon to apologize.
And Hae Yoon came to me to get
Chae Young's number to apologize.
For the first time, I thought you're getting married with a great woman.
She's very mature.
Do Hyun, I'd like to get some skin care at your hospital. Can I go?
You can come after 7.
In order to get custody, you need to build up a good relationship with your son.
I'm going to sleep with you in your room tonight, okay?
Yes!
Daddy.
Did you also come here to sleep with me?
Yes.
I'll be here. You can go sleep in you room.
How about the three of us sleep together?
Together.
What are you trying to do now?
You won't get custody any way.
We will see about that later.
What made us like this? I wanted to live a happy life with you.
Then just give up and obey me.
For you, this is a choice
that you can do or can't do.
If I see your face, I feel like throwing up.